With the 198th pick in the 2026 NFL
Draft, the Minnesota Vikings select
De'Mont Claiborne, running back, Wake
Forest.
Bucky, sometimes you go shopping, right?
And they see you got the little
clearance rack, and you go in and you're
like, "Ooh, how did this make it here?"
And it becomes [laughter] your shirt.
It becomes your shirt. This is what I'm
going to wear. And then you're like, "I
don't I stole this."
>> [music]
>> De'Mont Claiborne is that shirt on the
clearance rack because he's way better
than a sixth-round pick. Now, he's
undersized. So, he is he is a small
running back for sure, but he [music]
has rare acceleration and burst, and he
has some real home run potential.
Reminds me of a Keaton
Try to remember who played for the Jets.
Keaton Mitchell? Yeah. Oh, yeah, yeah,
yeah. That's who he reminds me of here
cuz when he gets going, it's juice city.